 
  
 
 
  
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
County of San Diego, Health and Human 
Services Agency, Public Health Services, 
Community Health Statistics Unit 
 
Prepared August 2025 
 
Persons Experiencing Homelessness 
in San Diego County, 2023-2025 
  
Page | i  
 
 
 
 
 
 
Persons Experiencing Homelessness   
in San Diego County, 2023 -2025  
August  202 5 
 
All materials in this document are in the public domain and may be reproduced and copied without 
permission. However, citation to source is appreciated. Suggested citation:  
County of San Diego, Health and Human Services Agency. Persons Experiencing Homeless in San 
Diego County, 2023-2025. August 2025.  
This publication Persons Experiencing Homeless in San Diego County, 2023-2025 utilizes estimated data 
that is current up through 2025 or the most current year available at the time this publication was in 
development. This document was developed under the Community Health Statistics Unit of the County 
of San Diego and is in support of Live Well San Diego. 
 
 
Inquiries regarding this document may be directed to: 
 
Community Health Statistics Unit 
5530 Overland Ave, 
San Diego, CA 92123 
(619) 692-6667 
 www.SDHealthStatistics.com 
 
 
 
 
 

  
Page | ii  
 
 Table of Contents 
Introduction .................................................................................................................................................. 1 
Homelessness in San Diego County .......................................................................................................... 1 
Definitions ................................................................................................................................................. 1 
Point-in-Time Count Data ............................................................................................................................. 3 
Persons Experiencing in Homelessness in San Diego County ................................................................... 3 
Trends Among Persons Experiencing Homelessness ............................................................................ 3 
Persons Experiencing Chronic Homelessness ....................................................................................... 4 
Families Experiencing Homelessness .................................................................................................... 5 
Youth Experiencing Homelessness ....................................................................................................... 6 
Veterans Experiencing Homelessness .................................................................................................. 7 
Unsheltered Counts by Subregional Area (SRA) ................................................................................... 8 
Students Experiencing Homelessness ........................................................................................................... 9 
Homeless Students in San Diego County .................................................................................................. 9 
Medical Encounters .................................................................................................................................... 11 
Emergency Department Discharges ........................................................................................................ 11 
Hospital Discharges ................................................................................................................................. 14 
Mortality ..................................................................................................................................................... 17 
Conclusion ................................................................................................................................................... 18 
References .................................................................................................................................................. 19 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
  
Page | iii  
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
This page is intentionally left blank. 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
Note: page 16 in AHAR for CA and US
  
Page | 1  
 
 
 
Homelessness in San Diego County 
In 202 4, t he United States was  home to over 338 
million people, where on a single night, 771,480  
people were experiencing homelessness. 1,2 Of the 
persons experiencing homelessness (PEH) in the 
United States in 2024, 24% were located in California, 
and 10,605 were located in San Diego County. 3 In 
2024, San Diego County had the second largest 
number of PEH in California and the seventh largest 
number of PEH in the United States. 2 PEH face a 
variety of health risks, including poverty, chronic 
disease, overcrowding in shelters,  poor mental 
health,  and substance use disorders.
4 Collection and 
examination of data identifying PEH and their health 
outcomes is crucial to understanding this 
populationÆs health disparities. 
 
This brief provides key take aways from the Persons 
Experiencing Homelessness in San Diego County 
Dashboard, 202 3-2025, located here: Persons 
Experiencing Homelessness in San Diego County, 
2023-2025 | Tableau Public . This includes data from 
the 2015-2025 Point-in-Time Count  for San Diego 
County, homeless student data from the 2023 -2024 
California Longitudinal Pupil Achievement Data  
System for San Diego County, the 202 3 California 
Health Care Access and Information (HCAI) data for  
medical encounters  among persons experiencing 
homelessness treated in a San Diego County facility, 
and the 202 3 Vital Records Business Intelligence 
System (V RBIS)  data among persons experiencing 
homelessness in San Diego County.  
 
Definitions 
Point-in-Time Count Definition2
Definitions of homelessness vary by data source. To 
be considered homeless in the Point-in-Time Count, 
a person needs to meet the definition of 
experiencing homelessness used by HUD2. It is 
defined as lacking a fixed, regular, 
 
 
Introduction 
In 2024, there were 187,084 persons 
experiencing homelessness in 
California, accounting for 24% of the 
US homeless population. 
In 2024, there were 771,480 persons 
experiencing homelessness in the  
United States (US).  
In 2024, there were 10,605 persons 
experiencing homelessness in San 
Diego County, accounting for 5.7% 
of CaliforniaÆs homeless population.  
 
  
Page | 2  
 
and adequate nighttime residence, meaning the following:  
ò An individual or family with a primary nighttime residence that is a public or private place not 
designed for or ordinarily used as a regular sleeping accommodation for human beings, 
including a car, park, abandoned building, bus or train station, airport, or camping ground; or 
ò An individual or family living in a supervised publicly or privately operated shelter designated to 
provide temporary living arrangements (including congregate shelters, transitional housing, and 
hotels and motels paid for by charitable organizations or by federal, State, or local government 
programs for low-income individuals). 
 
California Department of Education, California Longitudinal Pupil Achievement 
Data System (CALPADS) Definition5 
 
To be considered a homeless student in the CALPADS data, enrolled students must have reported 
experiencing homelessness at any point in time during the academic year. This includes students 
reporting residing in a hotel, motel, or a temporary shelter, living temporarily doubled-up, or were 
temporarily unsheltered.  
 
Department of Health Care Access and Information (HCAI) Definition6 
 
In the 2023 Department of Health Care Access and Information (HCAI) Emergency Department 
Discharge Data and Hospital Discharge data, a person was considered homeless if the homelessness 
indicator was marked æYesÆ, or an ICD-10 diagnosis code for reporting homelessness was included in the 
patient record. This includes Z59.00, Z59.01, and Z59.02.  
 
Vital Records Business Intelligence System (VBIS) Definition7 
 
In the data from the Vital Records and Business Intelligence System (VRBIS), a person was considered to 
have been experiencing homelessness if the homeless status as entered on death certificate field 25A 
was æYes.Æ 
 
Page | 3  
 
 
  
Persons Experiencing in Homelessness in San Diego County 
 
In 2025, there were 9,905 persons experiencing homelessness on any given night in San Diego County. 
Of those, over half (57.7%) were unsheltered, and 42.3% were sheltered.   
Trends Among Persons Experiencing Homelessness 
 
Overall, the number  of persons experiencing homelessness (PEH) has increased from 2015 to 2025.  
The number of PEH increased from 8,742 in 2015 to 9,905 in 2025. Similarly, the number  of 
unsheltered PEH increased from 4,156 in 2015 to 5,714 in 2025. The number of sheltered PEH 
decreased from 4,586 to 4,191.  
However, 2025 saw the first decrease in total PEH from the prior year since 2020.   
From 2024 to 2025, the number of  PEH decreased from 10,605 to 9,905. The  number of unsheltered 
PEH decreased from 6,110 in 2024 to 5,714 in 2025, and the number  of sheltered PEH decreased from 
4,495 in 202 4 to 4,191 in 202 5.  
 Point-in-Time Count Data 
Figure 1: Count of Persons Experiencing Homelessness in San Diego County, 2015-2025 
*The Point-in-Time Count was not conducted in 2021 due to the COVID-19 pandemic. 
Source: Regional Task Force on Homelessness, Point-in-Time Count, 2015-2025. 

Page | 4  
Persons Experiencing Chronic Homelessness 
An individual is considered chronically homeless i f the individual has a disability and has been 
continuously experiencing homelessness for one year or more or has experienced  at least four 
episodes of homelessness in the last three years where the combined length of time experiencing 
homelessness on those occasions is at least 12 months. 2  
ò In 2025, the chronically homeless population accounted for 40% of the homeless population in  
San Diego County. Over 65% of the chronically homeless population was unsheltered.
ò The number of individuals experiencing chronic homelessness has i ncreased every year from 
2023-2025.
ò The number of individuals experiencing chronic homelessness more than doubled from 2022  
(1,414) to 2023 (3,516). The majority of the increase was among unsheltered PEH.
Figure 2: Count of Persons Experiencing Chronic Homelessness, San Diego County, 2015-2025 
*The Point-in-Time Count was not conducted in 2021 due to the COVID-19 pandemic.
Source: Regional Task Force on Homelessness, Point-in-Time Count, 2015-2025. 
Page | 5  
Families Experiencing Homelessness 
A household is considered a family household experiencing homelessness if the household is made up 
of at least one adult aged 18 or older and one child under 18 years old that were experiencing 
homelessness together on the night of the point -in-time count.2  
ò In 2025, the number  of individuals in families experiencing homelessness accounted for 14%
of the total PEH population. A large majority of families experiencing homelessness were
sheltered (96%).
ò The total number of individuals in families experiencing homelessness has decreased from
1,981 in 2015 to 1,397 in 2025.
ò The number of individuals in families that were unsheltered remained relatively stable from
2015 to 2025.
Figure 3: Count of Families (Total Individuals) Experiencing Homelessness, San Diego County, 2025 
*The Point-in-Time Count was not conducted in 2021 due to the COVID-19 pandemic.
 Counts of individuals in families experiencing homelessness are not available by sheltered and unsheltered status for 2019-2020.  
Source: Regional Task Force on Homelessness, Point-in-Time Count, 2015-2025. 
Page | 6  
Youth Experiencing Homelessness 
Unaccompanied Youth/Children (under 18) are people in households with only children under the age 
of 18 who are not part of a family with children or accompanied by their parent  or guardian during 
their experience of homelessness. Unaccompanied Youth (18 -24) are young adults in households 
without children who are not part of a family with children or accompanied by their parent or 
guardian during their episode of homelessness. 2
ò In 2025, unaccompanied youth accounted for 7% of the PEH population. About 44% of
unaccompanied youth experiencing homelessness were unsheltered.
ò There was an increase in the total number of  youth experiencing homelessness from 2020 to
2024. However, the number decreased from 897 in 2024 to 682 in 2025.
ò Since 2022, sheltered individuals have made up a larger proportion of unaccompanied yout h
experiencing homelessness than unsheltered individuals.
Figure 4: Count of Youth Experiencing Homelessness, San Diego County, 2025 
*The Point-in-Time Count was not conducted in 2021 due to the COVID-19 pandemic.
Source: Regional Task Force on Homelessness, Point-in-Time Count, 2015-2025. 
Page | 7  
Veterans Experiencing Homelessness 
Veteran refers to any person who served on active duty in the armed forces of the United States. This 
includes Reserves and National Guard members who were called up to active duty. 2 Veterans are 
vulnerable to homelessness due to a variety of reasons, including military-r elated factors such as post-
traumatic stress disorder (PTSD),  traumatic brain injury (TBI), and military skills that may not be 
transferable to the civilian workforce. 8
ò In 2025, veterans accounted for 6% of the PEH population. Nearly 2 in 3 veterans experienci ng
homelessness were unsheltered, and over 1 in 3 were sheltered.
ò Overall, the number of veterans experiencing homelessness decreased from 1,381 in 2015 to
643 in 2025.
ò There were a higher number of unsheltered than sheltered veterans every year from 2022 to
2025.
Figure 5: Count of Veterans Experiencing Homelessness, San Diego County, 2025 
*The Point-in-Time Count was not conducted in 2021 due to the COVID-19 pandemic.
Source: Regional Task Force on Homelessness, Point-in-Time Count, 2015-2025. 
Page | 8  
Source: Regional Task Force on Homelessness, Point-in-Time Count, 2025. 
Unsheltered Counts by Subregional Area (SRA) 
Central San Diego  Subregional Area (SRA) had the greatest number of unsheltered persons 
experiencing homelessness in Central Region, and San Diego County overall. 
In 2025, about 1,700 unsheltered persons experiencing homelessness were counted in Central San 
Diego SRA. 
Figure 6: Unsheltered Point-in-Time Counts (PITCs) by Subregional Area (SRA), 
San Diego County, 2025 
 
Page | 9  
 
Source: California Department of Education, California Longitudinal Pupil Achievement Data System (CALPADS), 2023 -2024. 
 
 
 
Homeless Students in San Diego County 
 
  
 
In the 2023-2024 school year, there were 17,226 students experiencing homelessness in San 
Diego County. 
 
Among Subregional Areas (SRAs) in San Diego County, Southeastern San Diego had the greatest number 
of students experiencing homelessness (2,200), followed by Mid-City (1,675).  
 
 
 
 
 
 Students Experiencing Homelessness 
Figure 7: Homeless Student (Preschool-Adults) by Subregional Area (SRA),  
San Diego County, 2023-2024 
 
Page | 10  
 
Source: California Department of Education, Data Quest, 2023-24 Homeless 
Student Enrollment by Dwelling Type, San Diego County Report Disaggregated by 
Race/Ethnicity. Accessed 7/16/25. 
In the 2023-2024 school year, the 
majority of the homeless student 
population was Hispanic or Latino. 
 
The Hispanic/Latino population made 
up nearly 72% of the homeless student 
population, a proportion 1.4 times the 
proportion of the total student 
enrollment in San Diego County overall 
(49.5%). Black students made up 8.2% 
of the homeless student population, 
nearly twice the proportion of Black 
students in San Diego County overall 
(4.3%).  
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
In the 2023-2024 
school year, the 
majority of the 
homeless student 
population, 
regardless of 
race/ethnicity, 
was temporarily 
doubled-up. 
 
The Black 
homeless student 
population had 
the highest 
proportion of 
students living in 
hotels/motels 
(11.6%), the Asian 
homeless student 
population had 
the highest 
proportion of 
students living in 
temporary shelters (14.0%), and the White student population had the highest proportion of students 
who were temporarily unsheltered (7.7%). 
 
 
Figure 9: Homeless Student Count by Race/Ethnicity and Dwelling,  
San Diego County, 2023-2024 
Figure 8: Homeless Student Population by Race/Ethnicity, 
San Diego County, 2023-2024 
Source: California Department of Education, Data Quest, 2023-24 Homeless Student Enrollment by Dwelling 
Type, San Diego County Report Disaggregated by Race/Ethnicity. Accessed 7/16/25. 
 

 
Page | 11  
 
 
 
 
Hospitals in San Diego County are beginning to adopt the practice of indicating select social 
determinants of health in patientsÆ medical records through defined codes (ICD-10 Z codes). This 
information was utilized to examine hospital and emergency department (ED) discharge data for 
persons experiencing homelessness in 2023. 
Emergency Department Discharges 
In 2023, 12,453 persons experiencing homelessness were discharged from the Emergency Department 
(ED) in San Diego County. There was a total of 36,724 ED discharges in 2023, indicating an average of 
about 2.9 visits per person experiencing homelessness. 
Among PEH that were discharged from the ED, the highest number of discharges was among 45û64-
year-olds for both males and females. There were more male PEH discharged from the ED than female 
PEH. 
 Medical Encounters 
Figure 10: ED Discharges by Age and Sex, San Diego County, 2023 
Individuals with unknown gender or age are not included in count of gender by age.  
Source: California Department of Health Care Access and Information (HCAI), Emergency Department Discharge Data, 2023. 

 
Page | 12  
 
Among PEH discharged from the ED, the highest number of discharges was among non-Hispanic White 
PEH, followed by Hispanic, and non-Hispanic Black. 
Emergency Departments in zip code 92103 had the greatest number of emergency discharges of PEH 
(6,317 discharges) compared to other zip codes. The majority of PEH discharged from emergency 
departments in San Diego County in 2023 had Medi-Cal (9,211) or Health Maintenance Organization 
Medicare Risk (973) as the expected source of payment. 
The majority of PEH discharged from the 
emergency departments in San Diego 
County in 2023 were discharged to home or 
self-care (routine discharge) (10,980 
discharges) or left against medical advice 
or discontinued care (601 discharges).  
 
 
Figure 11: ED Discharges by Race/Ethnicity, San Diego County, 2023 
Figure 14: Emergency Department Discharges Among 
PEH by Top Three Patient Dispositions,  
San Diego County, 2023 
Figure 12: Emergency Department 
Discharges Among PEH by Top Five 
Facility Zip Codes,  
San Diego County, 2023 
Figure 13: Emergency Department Discharges Among 
PEH by Top Five Expected Sources of Payment,  
San Diego County, 2023 
AIAN: American Indian/Alaska Native. NHPI: Native Hawaiian/Pacific Islander. 
 Source: California Department of Health Care Access and Information (HCAI), Emergency Department Discharge Data, 2023.  
Source: California Department of Health Care Access and Information (HCAI), Emergency Department Discharge Data, 2023. 
Source: California Department of Health Care Access and Information (HCAI), 
Emergency Department Discharge Data, 2023. 

 
Page | 13  
 
The top diagnosis among PEH discharged from emergency departments in San Diego County was skin 
and subcutaneous tissue infections (837 discharges), followed by musculoskeletal pain, not low back 
pain (535 discharges), and alcohol-related disorders (510 discharges).  
The top diagnosis among Hispanic PEH discharged from emergency departments in San Diego County 
was skin and subcutaneous tissue 
infections (257 discharges), followed 
by abdominal pain and other 
digestive/abdomen signs and 
symptoms (169 discharges), and 
musculoskeletal pain, not low back 
pain (155 discharges). 
The top diagnosis among non-
Hispanic White PEH discharged from 
emergency departments in San 
Diego County was skin and 
subcutaneous tissue infections (435 
discharges), followed by alcohol-
related disorders (280 discharges), 
musculoskeletal pain, not low back 
pain (225 discharges), and suicidal 
ideation/attempt/intentional self-
harm (225 discharges). 
  
The top diagnosis among non-
Hispanic Black PEH discharged from emergency departments in San Diego County was musculoskeletal 
pain, not low back pain (115 discharges), followed by schizophrenia spectrum and other psychotic 
disorders (105 discharges), skin and subcutaneous tissue infections (87 discharges).  
Figure 15: Top 10 Primary Diagnoses Among PEH Discharged from Emergency Departments,  
San Diego County, 2023 
Figure 16: Top 3 Primary Diagnoses Among PEH Discharged 
from Emergency Departments by Race/Ethnicity, San Diego 
County, 2023 
Source: California Department of Health Care Access and Information (HCAI), Emergency Department Discharge Data, 2023. 
Source: California Department of Health Care Access and Information (HCAI), 
Emergency Department Discharge Data, 2023. 
 
Page | 14  
 
Hospital Discharges 
In 2023, 5,572 persons experiencing homelessness were discharged from a hospital in San Diego County. 
There was a total of 10,175 hospital discharges in 2023, indicating an average of 1.8 visits per person 
experiencing homelessness. 
 
Among PEH discharged from the hospital, the highest number of discharges was among 45û64-year-olds 
for both males and females. There were more male PEH discharged from the hospital than female PEH. 
 
 
Figure 17: Hospital Discharges by Age and Sex, San Diego County, 2023 
Individuals with unknown gender or age are not included in count of gender by age.  
Source: California Department of Healthcare Access and Information (HCAI), Patient Discharge Data, 2023. 
 
 

 
Page | 15  
 
Among PEH that were discharged from the hospital, the highest number of discharges was among non-
Hispanic White PEH, followed by Hispanic, and non-Hispanic Black.  
Hospitals in the zip code 92103 had the greatest number of discharges of PEH (2,556 discharges) 
compared to other zip codes. The majority of PEH discharged from hospitals in San Diego County in 2023 
had Medi-Cal (3,840 discharges) or Medicare (1,385) as the expected source of payment. 
 
The majority of PEH discharged 
from the hospitals in San Diego 
County in 2023 were 
discharged to home or self-
care (routine discharge) (3,376 
discharges) or were 
discharged/transferred to a 
skilled nursing facility (SNF) 
with Medicare certification in 
anticipation of skilled care (979 
discharges).  
Figure 18: Hospital Discharges by Race/Ethnicity, San Diego County, 2023 
Figure 21: Hospital Discharges Among PEH by Top Three Patient 
Dispositions, San Diego County, 2023 
Figure 19: Hospital Discharges Among PEH by 
Top Five Facility Zip Codes,  
San Diego County, 2023 
Figure 20: Hospital Discharges Among PEH by 
Top Five Expected Sources of Payment,  
San Diego County, 2023 
AIAN: American Indian/Alaska Native. NHPI: Native Hawaiian/Pacific Islander. 
Source: California Department of Healthcare Access and Information (HCAI), Patient Discharge Data, 2023. 
Source: California Department of Healthcare Access and Information (HCAI), Patient Discharge Data, 2023. 
Source: California Department of Healthcare Access and Information (HCAI), Patient Discharge 
Data, 2023. 

 
Page | 16  
 
Source: California Department of Healthcare Access and Information (HCAI), Patient Discharge Data, 2023. 
 
 
 
The top diagnosis among PEH discharged from hospitals in San Diego County was septicemia (848 
discharges), followed by skin and subcutaneous tissue infections (474 discharges), and heart failure (292 
discharges).  
 
The top diagnosis among 
Hispanic PEH discharged 
from hospitals in San Diego 
County was septicemia (224 
discharges), followed by skin 
and subcutaneous tissue 
infections (114 discharges), 
and diabetes mellitus with 
complication (73 discharges).  
 
The top diagnosis among 
non-Hispanic White PEH 
discharged from hospitals in 
San Diego County was 
septicemia (422 discharges), 
followed by skin and 
subcutaneous tissue 
infections (269 discharges), 
and alcohol-related 
disorders (168 discharges).  The top diagnoses among non-Hispanic Black PEH discharged from hospitals 
in San Diego County was septicemia (110 discharges), followed by heart failure (77 discharges) and skin 
and subcutaneous tissue infections (53 discharges).  
 
Figure 22: Top 10 Primary Diagnoses Among PEH Discharged from Hospitals,  
San Diego County, 2023 
Figure 23: Top 3 Primary Diagnoses Among PEH Discharged from 
Hospitals by Race/Ethnicity, San Diego County, 2023 
Source: California Department of Healthcare Access and Information (HCAI), Patient Discharge 
Data, 2023. 
 
Page | 17  
 
Table contains deaths that occurred in San Diego County. º Not shown for fewer than 11 deaths. NH: Non-Hispanic. Source: California Department 
of Public Health, Centers for Health Statistics, Office of Health Information and Research, Vital Records Business Intelligen ce System, 2023. 
  
 
 
 
  
 
The top three leading causes of death among persons experiencing homelessness in San Diego County in 
2023 were accidents/unintentional injuries, heart disease, and cancer. The unsheltered population 
made up 83.8% of the deaths in 2023 among PEH. 
 
Sex 
 
Males made up the majority of the deaths among 
PEH (78.8%).  
 
Age 
 
Nearly half of the deaths among PEH were among 
those aged 50-69 (47.5%). 
 
Race/Ethnicity 
 
The Non-Hispanic White population accounted 
for 62.5% of deaths among PEH, followed by 
Hispanic (21.3%), and Non-Hispanic Black 
(11.7%).  
 
 
 
 
 
 
Rank is based on total number of deaths in each of the National Center for Health Statistics (NCHS) "rankable" categories. The top 3 leading 
causes of death presented here are based on deaths that occurred in San Diego for their respective years. Cause of death is based on the 
underlying cause of death reported on death certificates as classified by ICD-10 codes. Source: California Department of Public Health, Center 
for Health Statistics, Office of Health Information and Research, Vital Records Business Intelligence System.  
Figure 24: Deaths Among Persons Experiencing 
Homelessness in San Diego County, 2023 
Mortality 
240 
 
Page | 18  
 
 
 
Homelessness continues to increase across the United States, California, and San Diego County. Lack of 
adequate and stable housing exacerbates existing health problems and can cause new ones, including 
chronic disease, poor mental health, and increased complications following infection or injury. 
Collection and examination of data identifying persons experiencing homelessness and their health 
outcomes is crucial to understanding the populationÆs health disparities. These data may inform 
decisions regarding targeted resources and interventions. 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 Conclusion 
 
 
Page | 19  
 
 
1. United States Census Bureau, U.S. and World Population Clock and Population Estimates, 2024. 
Accessed July 29, 2025. https://www.census.gov/popclock/   
 
2. United States Department of Housing and Urban Development (HUD), Office of Community 
Planning and Development, The 2024 Annual Homelessness Assessment Report (AHAR) to 
Congress, December 2024. 
https://www.huduser.gov/portal/sites/default/files/pdf/2024-AHAR-Part-1.pdf  
 
3. Regional Task Force on Homelessness, Point-in-Time Count, 2015-2025.  
https://www.rtfhsd.org/reports-data/  
 
4. National Health Care for the Homeless Council, Frequently Asked Questions, 
2022. https://nhchc.org/understanding-homelessness/faq/ 
5. California Department of Education, California Longitudinal Pupil Achievement Data System 
(CALPADS), 2023-2024. https://www.cde.ca.gov/ds/ad/hseinfo.asp 
 
6. California Department of Health Care Access and Information, Emergency Department Discharge 
and Patient Discharge Database, 2023. 
7. California Department of Public Health, Centers for Health Statistics, Office of Health Information 
and Research, Vital Records Business Intelligence System, 2023. 
  
8. Olenick M, Flowers M, Diaz VJ. US veterans and their unique issues: enhancing health care 
professional awareness. Adv Med Educ Pract. 2015 Dec 1;6:635-9. doi: 10.2147/AMEP.S89479. 
PMID: 26664252; PMCID: PMC4671760. 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
  
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 References 
 
Page | 20  
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
  
 


